(Penny:)all with erectile dysfunction,
you didn't get your part cut!
(Leonard:)Hey. Can we talk?
(Penny:)We can, but the part
of Penny might get cut.
(Leonard:)That was really crappy of me.
(Leonard:)What you're trying to do is hard,
but people do make it,
(Leonard:)and I really do believe
you could be one of them.
(Penny:)Thank you.
(Leonard:)And... to show you how much
I believe in you,
(Leonard:)I kind of got you an audition.
(Penny:)Are you serious? For what?
(Leonard:)-The new Star Wars movie.
-What?!
(Penny:)-How did you manage that?
-There's this thing online,
(Leonard:)you put yourself on tape and just
send it in, anyone can do it.
(Penny:)Come on, Leonard,
this is just a PR stunt.
(Leonard:)So? Even if it is,
you have a huge advantage
(Leonard:)because you're an actual actress.
(Leonard:)Most of the people doing this
are just weirdoes and nerds.